itnt.co.za 2011-11-03

# In The Net Technologies, InTheNet Technologies - Enterprise Anti-spam, adsl, diginet, email, dns, connectivity, free fax, Web development,web site design,graphic design,HTML,Flash,ASP,Java programming,Visual Basic,Delphi,application development,SQL,Access,database development,e-commerce solutions, website design

ITNT is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the ITNT site (the “Site”). By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information thats personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested such as receiving information about ITNT products and services, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site or service, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering ITNT products.

The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, work or home address, information about your job function, information about your company, and credit card information.

The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.

In support of these uses, ITNT may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related ITNT products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with ITNT, information collected by ITNT may be combined with information collected by other ITNT services.

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other ITNT products and services, and/or share information with ITNT partners so they may send you information about their products and services.

We merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content.

When you sign up for a newsletter or agree to receive promotional e-mail, ITNT may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. Each e-mail communication includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication.

ITNT occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

ITNT may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ITNT or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ITNT and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of ITNT employees or agents, users of ITNT products or services, or members of the public.

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the UK or any other country in which ITNT or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**Control of your Personal Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of ITNT and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. As described below in the next section, you can access your personal information and make choices about how you wish to be contacted.

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to ITNT in the context of other, separately operated, ITNT products or services.

ITNT may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. In some services offered by ITNT, contact with the customer is an intrinsic part of the service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service(s) you have chosen.

**Access to your Personal Information**  
You can review and edit the personal information and contact preferences you provided at this Site by logging in to your account profile.

You will be asked to enter your user name and password before viewing your personal information. Some services offered on ITNT may collect information that is not accessible via the account profile. However, in such cases, you can access your personal information by contacting ITNT as described at the bottom of this statement, or through alternative means of access described by the service.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
ITNT is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Protection of Children's Personal Information**  
ITNT is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

**Use of Cookies**  
We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized.

Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about ITNT Web site usage, such as how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a ITNT Web page or a newsletter. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies but do not allow other companies to place clear gifs or cookies on our sites unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into ITNT a site that relies on third-party cookies or clear gifs).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit.

**Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**  
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact [info@itnt.co.za](mailto:info@itnt.co.za)

**Changes to this Statement**  
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our Web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**Contact Information**  
ITNT welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that ITNT has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us via the Site or via email address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
